## Shalom Dawit

Shalom.Dawit@Gmail.Com | (203) 626-1841 | LinkedIn | Github | Portfolio | Suffield, CT | he/him/his

## Summary

History of great customer service and working in a fast paced environment. Superior relationship-building skills and experience working collaboratively with end-users and management.

Skills (Years of experience listed after each item.)

Languages: HTML 5 | JavaScript 4 | C# 0.5 Frameworks: React 2 | Node.JS 2 | Jest 0.2

Databases: MySQL 2 | MongoDB 1

Other: Git 3 | Agile 1

#### Education

School of Engineering Coding Bootcamp, FullStack Developer, Graduation: 01/2021 University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT

Junior Credits in Electrical Engineering

## Experience

WaShinRyu Jujutsu - Albuquerque, NM | Site Maintainer, PM | 08/2017 - Present

- Manage website and Facebook media activity
- •Deal with all billing (server and domain), frontend and backend issues related to the site

Image Works - Westport, CT | IT, Website Support | 08/2017 - Present

- Maintain website while troubleshooting frontend and backend issues
- Helped with designing of website

Manchester Public Schools - Manchester, CT | Math Tutor, Coordinator, Long-Term Sub | 05/2019 - Present

- Math Tutor for 9-12th Grades and Classes
- Program Coordinator for Pilot Student Internship Program

#### **Projects**

The ToolShed Open Source

- ●Maintainer and lead engineer for The ToolShed, a React app to help users organize their tools
- ●Technologies Used: React, ExpressJS, NodeJS, Sequelize, Cors, Dotenv, CSS3, Bootstrap, Heroku Recipe Tracker Open Source

App to organize recipes

# **Shalom Dawit**

●Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript E6+, JQuery, ESLint, Passport, Nodemailer, Bcrypt, Express-Handlebars

Cov19 Info | Open Source

- ●Covid-19 high level statistics dashboard
- Technologies Used: Materialize, Third-Party API (Covid-19 info api & NYTimes article-search api), HTML5, AJAX, JavaScript

#### Awards & Certifications

- Remarkable Employee Award at Illing Middle School & Manchester High-School
- •Mentor and licensed instructor for a martial arts club & course at the University of Connecticut